Guide to the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI. U.S. Security and Exchanges Commission (SEC) Files, 1972-2007 [Bulk Dates: 1990-2004]
  - Chronological Files--Grouped Files
    - 1990-1993
      - IRRC News for Investors, 1992 March (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - Kimba Wood Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - Legal Times--Mary Shapiro, SEC, 1993 June (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Meeting with S. Wallman, SEC, 1991 April (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Proposed Rule Changes, 1992 (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 9 to 10)
      - Proxy Rules Review, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - SEC, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 34)
      - SEC Alert--AT&T Meeting, 1992 June (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - SEC Alerts, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 35)
      - SEC Brief, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - SEC Campaigns Round Two, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - SEC Court Case, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 37)
      - SEC Press Releases, 1993 October (Box 82, Folder 38)
      - SEC Rule Changes--Solicitation and Executive Compensation, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - SEC Rule Changes, Shareholding Information, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Senate Banking Letter, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 36)
      - Standard Letters, circa 1992 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - Tilt, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Update, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Walmart
        - Our T Case Equal Opportunity Employment (EEO), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
        - Walmart Court Case, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 33)
        - SEC--Decision for Faxing, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        - SEC--Appeal of Judge Woods’ Decision, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union et al vs. Walmart--Brief, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 1994-1995
      - Action Packet, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Case, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence with SEC Chair, Arthur Levitt, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Meeting with Commissioner Wallman, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Member Letters to Congress Re: 2 Vacancies on the SEC, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Member Letters to President Clinton and Vice-President Al Gore Re: SEC Vacancies, 1994-1997 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Rule Revisions, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - SEC Council Addresses, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 39)
      - SEC “Tilt,” 1994 (Box 82, Folder 40)
      - SEC Letters to Levitt, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 41)
      - SEC Action Alert, 1995 January 22 (Box 82, Folder 42)
      - Senate and Other House Letter (Fr. Members), 1994 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - 1995-1996
      - Council of Institutional Investors--Committee on Shareholder Proposal Reform (SEC Committee), 1995-1996 (Box 82, Folder 44)
      - Letter to President Clinton et al., 1996 (Box 82, Folder 46)
      - Robert Reich and SEC Campaign, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 45)
      - Rule 14-a-4, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - SEC Campaign, 1996 Summer (Box 82, Folder 43)
      - SEC Challenges, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - 1996-1998
      - Allied Signal
        - Challenge, 1997 February (Box 34, Folder 36)
        - Responses to Refusal to Hear Challenge to “No Action” on Allied Signal, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - American Society of Corporate Secretaries “Shareholder Reform,” 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Campaign Letters Re: December 4, 1996 Alert, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Challenges, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Congressional Black Caucus, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Congressional Hearings, 1997 March (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Council of Institutional Investors (CII)--SEC Initiative, 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 49)
      - Home Depot, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Index of Briefs and Correspondence Re: 1997 Proxy Proposals, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - Index of Files Containing Briefs and Correspondence Relating to 1997 Proxy Proposals, 1997 January 25 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - (Investor Responsibility Research Center) IRRC Analysis, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Letter from 35 Congresspersons to SEC, 1996 October 10 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Letter Sent to 35 Congresspersons, 1996 August 29 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Letter to Alphonse D’Amato, 1997 January 28 (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Letters to Commissioners, 1996 December 31 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Letter to Congressional Black Caucus (CBC) and Other Congresspersons, 1997 January 24 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Letters to Hunt and Johnson, 1996 August 21 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Letters to President Clinton, 1997 August (Box 82, Folder 50)
      - Letters to President Clinton and SEC, 1997 August (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Letters to SEC, 1997 January-May (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - “Masters” for SEC Alerts, 1997 January (Box 82, Folder 48)
      - National Securities Markets Improvement Act of 1996, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Neuhauser Appeals, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Nike--SEC Challenge, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 53)
      - Procedures for Responding to Companies (CO’s) Requests to SEC for No Action Letters, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Responses to SEC--A-Z, 1998 (2 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 12 to 13)
      - Resolutions Withdrawn, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Phil Roberts--Free Burma Campaign of Takoma Park, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Mr. Rodgers and the Nun (Sister Doris Gurmley), 1996 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Rule Changes, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - SEC
        - Alert, 1997 July 9 (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 48)
        - Annual General Meeting (AGM), 1997 (Box 34, Folder 49)
        - Appeal, 1997 January 31 (Box 34, Folder 50)
        - Highlights and Proposed Action Plan, 1997 May (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - SEC Challenges, 1997 (1 Folder) (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - SEC Challenges, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - SEC Challenges and Responses, 1997
        - A (Box 79, Folder 3)
        - C-F (3 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 1 to 3)
        - G-M (7 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 2)
        - N-V (8 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 4 to 11)
          (No “Q”)
      - SEC Challenges and Rulings, 1997-1998 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - SEC Decisions, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - SEC Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 51)
      - SEC Rules Review Discussion, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 47)
      - Shareholder Process Review--Articles and Notes, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 52)
      - Society of Corporate Secretaries, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 52)
      - U.S. Trust Boston Op-Ed--Tim Smith, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Wallman
        - Response Letters to Wallman’s Speech, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 26)
        - Letter to Wallman, 1996 August 23 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - 1999
      - 1998-1999 SEC Challenges (List), 1999 February 1 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Responses to SEC (3 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 15 to 17)
      - SEC Responses (3 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 18 to 20)
    - 2000
      - Resolution Filings, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Resolutions, 2000 (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Burma, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3 to 5)
      - SEC Challenges--A-Z, 2000 (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 6 to 7)
      - SEC Challenges, 2000 (3 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 21 to 23)
    - 2001
      - Resolutions, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 2002-2004
      - Filing Letters
        - 2002 (Box 80, Folder 8)
        - Late Filing Letters, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 9)
        - 2004 (5 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 10 to 14)
      - Proxy Resolutions, 2003-2004
        - ICCR Actions and All Players, 2003 December (Box 48, Folder 43)
          (Lists)
        - Resolutions
          - General, 2003-2004 (6 Folders) (Box 48, Folder 44)
          - Global Warming (Box 48, Folder 45)
          - South Africa and General (Box 48, Folder 46)
          - Withdrawals (Box 48, Folder 47)
        - Abbott
          - General (Box 47, Folder 1)
          - HIV/AIDS Reporting (Box 47, Folder 2)
          - Political Contributions (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - AEP--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - AGCO--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - AIG
          - Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 6)
          - HIV/AIDS Reporting (Box 47, Folder 7)
          - Tobacco Investments (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - Alcoa--Pay Disparity (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - Alltel--Sexual Orientation Nondiscrimination (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - Altria
          - Canadian Warnings--Voluntary Use in US (Box 47, Folder 11)
          - Filters (Box 47, Folder 12)
          - Pregnant Women (Box 47, Folder 13)
        - Amgen
          - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box 47, Folder 14)
          - Interim Storage of Radioactive Waste (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - Anadarko--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 16)
        - Apache--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 17)
        - Archer-Daniels-Midland (ADM)--Genetically Modified Organism (GMO) (Box 47, Folder 18)
        - Avon
          - Annual Elections (Box 47, Folder 19)
          - Parabens (Box 47, Folder 20)
          - Phthalates (Box 47, Folder 21)
        - Bank of America
          - International Community Reinvestment Act (CRA) (Box 47, Folder 22)
          - Merger (Box 47, Folder 23)
        - Bed, Bath and Beyond--Glass Ceiling (Box 47, Folder 24)
        - BellSouth--Annual Elections (Box 47, Folder 25)
        - BJ--Burma (Box 47, Folder 26)
        - Boeing
          - Ethical Criteria for Contracts (Box 47, Folder 27)
          - Human Rights (HR) Policies (Box 47, Folder 28)
        - Bristol-Myers Squibb
          - Access (Box 47, Folder 29)
          - HIV/AIDS (Box 47, Folder 30)
          - Political Contributions (Box 47)
        - Burlington--Indigenous Peoples (Box 47, Folder 31)
        - Caterpillar
          - HIV/AIDS Reporting (Box 47, Folder 32)
          - Human Rights? (Box 47, Folder 33)
        - Cendant--CEO Pay (Box 47, Folder 34)
        - Chevron
          - AIDS (Box 47, Folder 35)
          - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR) (Box 47, Folder 36)
          - Renewable Energy (Box 47, Folder 37)
        - Chubb--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 38)
        - Cigna--Tobacco Investments (Box 47, Folder 39)
        - Cinergy--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 40)
        - Citi--International Community Reinvestment Act (CRA) (Box 47, Folder 41)
        - Coca-Cola--HIV/AIDS (Box 47, Folder 42)
        - Colgate--Human Rights (Box 47, Folder 43)
        - Conoco--Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR) (Box 47, Folder 44)
        - Cooper Cameron--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 45)
        - Cooper Industries--Sustainability (Box 47, Folder 46)
        - Costco
          - Annual Election (Box 47, Folder 47)
          - Land Procurement (Box 47, Folder 48)
        - CVS--Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO) Reporting (Box 47, Folder 49)
        - Danaher--Board Diversity (Box 47, Folder 50)
        - Delphi
          - Global Standards (Box 47, Folder 51)
          - Tobacco Investments (Box 47, Folder 52)
        - Delta--CEO Pay (Box 47, Folder 53)
        - Dillards--Human Rights (Box 47, Folder 54)
        - Dover--Sexual Orientation Nondiscrimination (Box 47, Folder 55)
        - Dow Chemical
          - Bhopal (Box 47, Folder 56)
          - Toxins (Box 47, Folder 57)
        - El Paso--Pay Disparity (Box 47, Folder 58)
        - Eli Lilly
          - Affordable Prescription Drugs (Box 47, Folder 59)
          - HIV/AIDS? (Box 47, Folder 60)
        - EOG--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 61)
        - EW Scripps--Newsroom Diversity (Box 47, Folder 62)
        - Excel--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 63)
        - Exxon
          - AIDS (Box 47, Folder 64)
          - Global Warming (2 Folders) (Box 47, Folder 65)
          - International Labor Organization (ILO) (Box 47, Folder 66)
          - Sexual Orientation Nondiscrimination (Box 47, Folder 67)
          - Renewable Energy (Box 47, Folder 68)
        - Fleet Bank
          - International Community Reinvestment Act (CRA) (Box 47, Folder 69)
          - Merger (Box 47, Folder 70)
        - FMC--Board Diversity (Box 47, Folder 71)
        - Ford
          - AIDS (Box 47, Folder 72)
          - Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 73)
        - General Dynamics--Foreign Military Sales (Box 47, Folder 74)
        - General Electric (GE)
          - Pay Disparity (Box 47, Folder 75)
          - PCBs (Box 47, Folder 76)
          - Smoke-Movies (Box 47, Folder 77)
          - Sustainability (Box 47, Folder 78)
        - General Motors--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 79)
        - Genuine Parts--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 80)
        - Gillette--Annual Elections (Box 47, Folder 81)
        - Grant Pride--Board Diversity (Box 47, Folder 82)
        - Honeywell--Pay Disparity (Box 47, Folder 83)
        - Intel--Water Use (Box 47, Folder 84)
        - International Paper--CEO Pay (Box 47, Folder 85)
        - Johnson and Johnson
          - General (Box 47, Folder 86)
          - HIV/AIDS (Box 47, Folder 87)
        - J.P. Morgan
          - Derivatives (Box 47, Folder 88)
          - Impact on Environment (Box 47, Folder 89)
          - Pay Disparity (Box 47, Folder 90)
        - Kellogg--Genetically Modified Organisms (GMOs) (Box 47, Folder 91)
        - Keycorp--Subprime Lending (Box 47, Folder 92)
        - Kerr McGee--Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) (Box 47, Folder 93)
        - Kinder Morgan--Board Diversity (Box 47, Folder 94)
        - Kohl’s--Sexual Orientation Nondiscrimination (Box 47, Folder 95)
        - Kroger--Sustainability (Box 47, Folder 96)
        - Kraft--Coffee Crisis (Box 47, Folder 97)
        - Lehman
          - Predatory Lending (Box 47, Folder 98)
          - Private Prison (Box 47, Folder 99)
        - Lockheed--Ethical Criteria for Contracts (Box 47, Folder 100)
        - Loews
          - Environmental Tobacco Smoke (ETS) (Box 47, Folder 101)
          - Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) (Box 47, Folder 102)
          - Lite Cigarettes (Box 47, Folder 103)
        - Longs--Separate Chairman and CEO (Box 47, Folder 104)
        - Marathon--Global Warming (Box 47, Folder 105)
        - MDC--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 106)
        - Merck
          - HIV (Box 47, Folder 107)
          - Patents (Box 47, Folder 108)
          - Political Contributions (Box 47, Folder 109)
        - MetLife--CEO Pay (Box 47, Folder 110)
        - Monsanto--Genetically Modified Organisms (GMO) Reporting (Box 47, Folder 111)
        - Newmont--Sustainability? (Box 47, Folder 112)
        - Northfork--Board Diversity (Box 47, Folder 113)
        - Northrop--Ethical Criteria for Contracts (Box 47, Folder 114)
        - NVR--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 115)
        - Occidental--Human Rights (Box 47, Folder 116)
        - OGE--Sexual Orientation Nondiscrimination (Box 47, Folder 117)
        - Pepsi America--Environmental Reporting (Box 47, Folder 118)
        - Pepsico--HIV (Box 47, Folder 119)
        - Pfizer
          - General (Box 47, Folder 120)
          - HIV/AIDS Reporting (Box 47, Folder 121)
          - Political Contributions (Box 47, Folder 122)
        - Principal--Tobacco Investments (Box 47, Folder 123)
        - Raytheon--Ethical Criteria for Contracts (Box 47, Folder 124)
        - Rite Aid--Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO) (Box 47, Folder 125)
        - R.J. Reynolds
          - Environmental Tobacco Smoke (ETS) (Box 47, Folder 126)
          - Tobacco Smuggling (Box 47, Folder 127)
        - Ruby Tuesday (Box 47, Folder 128)
        - Ryland--Environmental Risk Disclosure (Box 47, Folder 129)
        - Safeway--Genetically Modified Organisms (GMO) (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - Saks--Vendor Standards (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - Saks/Costco/99 Cents/Big Lots--Vendor Standards (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - SBC--Annual Elections (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - Schering Plough--Payments and Rebate Policies (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - Skywest--Board Diversity (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - Smith--Board Divsersity (Box 48, Folder 7)
        - Southern--Global Warming (Box 48, Folder 8)
        - Stanley--Annual Elections (Box 48, Folder 9)
        - Sysco--Genetically Modified Organisms (GMO) (Box 48, Folder 10)
        - Target--Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - Textron--Foreign Military Sales (FMS) (Box 48, Folder 12)
        - Time Warner
          - Pay Disparity (Box 48, Folder 13)
          - Political Contributions (Box 48, Folder 14)
          - Public Obligations (Box 48, Folder 15)
          - Teen Tobacco (Box 48, Folder 16)
        - TJX
          - Annual Elections (Box 48, Folder 17)
          - Vendor Standards (Box 48, Folder 18)
        - Torchmark--Tobacco Investments (Box 48, Folder 19)
        - Tribune--Political Contributions (Box 48, Folder 20)
        - TXU--Global Warming (Box 48, Folder 21)
        - Tyco--Environmental Reporting (Box 48, Folder 22)
        - Tyson--One Vote (Box 48, Folder 23)
        - United Technologies--Ethical Criteria for Contacts (Box 48, Folder 24)
        - Unocal--Global Warming (Box 48, Folder 25)
        - UST--Nitrosamines (TSNA) (Box 48, Folder 26)
        - Valero--Global Warming (Box 48, Folder 27)
        - VF Corporation--International Labor Organization (ILO) Code (Box 48, Folder 28)
        - Viacom
          - CEO Pay (Box 48, Folder 29)
          - Public Obligations (Box 48, Folder 30)
          - Teen Tobacco (Box 48, Folder 31)
        - Visteon--Global Standards (Box 48, Folder 32)
        - Wal-Mart
          - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO) (Box 48, Folder 33)
          - Genetically Modified Organisms (GMOs) (Box 48, Folder 34)
          - Sustainability (Box 48, Folder 35)
        - Werner--Board Diversity (Box 48, Folder 36)
        - Weyerhaeuser--Old Growth (Box 48, Folder 37)
        - Wyeth--Access (Box 48, Folder 38)
        - Yum
          - Annual Elections (Box 48, Folder 39)
          - Genetically Modified Organisms (GMOs) (Box 48, Folder 40)
          - Smoke Free (Box 48, Folder 41)
          - Sustainability (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - 2007
      - Action--Shareholders Rights, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Series VII: Publications, 1974-2011
  This series is primarily comprised of two publications, The Corporate Examiner newsletter, and the Proxy Resolutions Book. Both publications are incomplete, but the archive includes significant runs of both publications.
  The Corporate Examiner was started by the Corporate Information Center (CIC), and serves as the primary membership newsletter for the ICCR. However, annual reports and other special publications have also been published as issues of the Corporate Examiner. The Proxy Resolutions Book presents the texts of socially responsible shareholder resolutions filed each year by ICCR's faith-based investors.
  - 40th Anniversary Event Program, 2011 September 22 (Box 74)
  - Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 74)
    (Includes “A Faithful Choice for Justice: ICCR and 40 years of Shareholder Advocacy”)
  - Annual Reports
    See: The Corporate Examiner
  - Church Investments & War Profits: Clergy and Laymen Concerned, 1971 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Church Proxy Resolutions, 1988, 1993 (Box 74)
    (Continued by The Proxy Resolutions Book)
  - The Corporate Examiner
    (Newsletter. Note that ICCR Annual Reports were published as issues of The Corporate Examiner through at least 2002.)
    - Volumes 3-5, 1974-1976 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 3 Number 11; Volume 4 Numbers 2, 7)
    - Volumes 6-8, 1977-1979 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 6 Number 7)
    - Volumes 9-11, 1980-1982 (Box 74)
    - Volumes 12-14, 1983-1985 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 13 Number 6)
    - Volumes 15-18, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 15 Number 8; Volume 16 Number 7; Volume 17 Numbers 1, 2, 3;Volume 18 Number 2)
    - Volumes 19-21, 1990-1992 (Box 74)
    - Volumes 22-24, 1993-1995 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 22 Number 2)
    - Volumes 25-27, 1996-1998 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 25 Numbers 1, 6; Volume 27 Numbers 1, 2, 3, 4, 7)
    - Volumes 28-31, 1999-2003 (Box 74)
      (Missing Volume 31 Numbers 7, 8, 9, 10)
  - Corporate Responsibility and Religious Institutions: Information and Documents, 1971 April (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Diversity Workbook Designed for ICCR, 1999 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Don’t Get Burned: The Risks of Investing in New Coal-Fired Facilities, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - ICCR’s Social Sustainability Resource Guide: Building Sustainable Communities Through Multi-Party Collaboration, 2011 (Box 74)
  - The Proxy Resolutions Book, 1994-1995, 1997-1998, 2000-2004 (Box 74)
    (Continues Church Proxy Resolutions)
- Series VIII. Member & Subscriber Services, 1995-2003
  This series includes information on associates, members, subscribers, and on mailings made to these groups.
  - Subseries VIII.1 Associate and Subscriber Files, 1995-2003
    The files for associates and subscribers include information on subscriptions to the Corporate Examiner and other mailings. The files also include an incomplete set of mailings for 1996-2002. The mailings consisted of informational materials produced outside of ICCR that were distributed to subscribers. The files include a cover list with a checklist of materials in each mailing, copies of these materials, and a form for ordering additional materials on related topics.
    - Alternative Investments Newsletter, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Mailings
      - 1996 December (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - 1998
        - January (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - March (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - April (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - June (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - July (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - August (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - October (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - 1999
        - January (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - March (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - May (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - June (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - August (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - December (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - 2000
        - March (Box 40, Folder 15)
        - June (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - 2002 July and November (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1999-2003 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Subscriber Services
      - 1996 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - 1995-2002 (7 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 45 to 51)
  - Subseries VIII.2 Membership Files, 1995-2002
    The membership files are arranged alphabetically by organization, and include information on dues and pledges.
    - Associates (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - New Members (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Adorers of the Blood of Christ (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Adrian Dominican Sisters (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - American Baptist Churches--Home Mission Society (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Amnesty International (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Archdiocese of Milwaukee (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - As You Sow Foundation (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Atonement Friars (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Baal & Gainer (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Baboon Family (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Beezer, M. Allison (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Benedictine Heath Resource Center (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Bon Secours Heath System (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - BSCH International (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Business for Social Responsibility (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Calvert New Africa Fund (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Calvert Social Investment Fund (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Capital Investment Services of America, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Carlisle Social Investments (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Catholic Center, The (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Catholic Community Foundation (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Catholic Foundation / Aquinas Fund (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Catholic Health East (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Catholic Healthcare West (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Catholic Health Initiatives (Formerly Franciscan Health System) (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Catholic Relief Services (Box 31, Folder 28)